[TALIA] So we are continuing this campaign
with our next partner,
Billy Cariño of LoveList.
[BILLY] LoveList stands where it is today
because of my team,
my best friend,
my LoveList family,
and my family.
[BEA] I've done everything I can
to give my mother a good life.
[BEA SNIFFLES]
What's happening?
I'm back to square one.
Billy.
Again, I'm sorry.
You know that I love you very much, right?
You're gonna let me see Papa again?
Mm.
Thank you, Billy!
- Thank you.
- Mmm!
Thank you, thank you!
I hope you can forgive me, Precious.
I never meant to hurt you.
I didn't come here
to listen to your explanation.
- But, Pres--
- Listen.
Billy agreed. You can meet with Oliver
after his classes are over.
4:30 to 5:30.
You can meet up at your house.
[JORDAN]
Are you sure about your decision?
My brother's all grown up.
I just want to give him the chance
to meet his father,
even just for a little while.
Then it's up to him
after he gets to know him.
I wish I had your courage.
I'm really sorry.
Let's go.
[WOMAN] What the hell?!
The road is so wide!
- [MARIELA] Just get out of here! Idiot!
- [WOMAN] Dang it!
- [MAN] Come on.
- Idiot!
[MAN] Let's go.
Mariela?
I saw my husband.
The one who hasn't contacted me in years.
[KNOCK AT DOOR]
[PRECIOUS] Mariela?
Bea?
[LYDIA] Sis, let's just leave.
[BILLY] You saw how happy
he was earlier, didn't you?
[NO AUDIBLE DIALOG]
Didn't I tell you
that decision was for Oliver?
But is it the right choice?
Well, we'll never know unless we try.
Okay then. Bye-bye.
Auntie Pres.
Are you all right?
[MELLOW MUSIC PLAYING]
["ABELYANA" BY MAKI PLAYING]
["ABELYANA" CONTINUES]
[JORDAN] We've known
each other for so long.
There are good times
and bad.
We've seen it all.
["ABELYANA" CONTINUES]
[JORDAN] And I can't help
but admire how you rose above it.
I can't help
but fall.
["ABELYANA" CONTINUES]
[JORDAN] I can't help
but fear losing you.
So let me take this chance to say…
I think I love you.
And if someday, life gets heavy,
or when the road is hard to see,
when your world is full of questions,
you can always run to me.
["ABELYANA" CONTINUES]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
Auntie Pres, even if you were trespassing,
what she did was still wrong!
We should report her!
You got hurt.
Are you all right?
I'm all right, Billy.
But you have to look at this.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[PRECIOUS] We were shocked
when we saw that there.
So they've been keeping
an eye on me for a while now?
Auntie Pres, right from the start,
they've been planning this all along.
That's why we need to be more careful.
[PRECIOUS] We don't know why
they're going after you.
The only thing we can be sure of is that
Mariela and Bea are both dangerous.
And now, we have proof
that they are not in their right minds.
[EXHALES SHARPLY] Billy, I'm sorry.
I just really wanted to help you
lessen your problems,
and find out why they're so mad at you.
But it seems that
I've only made things worse.
[FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING]
[CRISELDA] Look at what you've done!
- My God, I was panicking.
- [BEA] Hey! What's happening here?
[CRISELDA]
What if you'd actually killed her?
[BEA] Ma! Wait a minute.
What's happening here?
We should be the ones asking you that.
I'll let you sleep here
in my unit for tonight,
but you should be gone by the morning!
Wait, Ms. Criselda. Don't do this to us.
You haven't paid rent
for two months already!
If I'd only known that you were criminals,
I never would have let you live here!
Wait a second. Please watch
your mouth, Ms. Criselda.
Who are you calling criminals?
Your mother almost murdered someone!
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[BEA] Ma?
What?
Why are you still standing there, huh?
The show's over, okay?
Stop watching us, you nosy bastards.
Go home!
How crazy.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Ma.
[BEA] Ma.
What was Ms. Criselda talking about?
You almost murdered someone?
[PAPER RUSTLING]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Um…
That's for next month's rent.
Oh.
Where did you get this?
It's from the last salary you gave me.
What about the month after that?
Where will you get the money then?
I'll just find a way.
I can talk to Ma'am Ronquillo.
So you're not going to leave anymore?
Billy gave me the chance to see Oliver.
[ENRICO] It's also my chance
to make it up to them.
I hope this is the start of my children
letting me into their lives again.
I'm really happy for you, Eric.
Thank you.
[CHUCKLES]
[CRYING] They're living lavishly.
They have a beautiful house.
They're living a luxurious life.
And now, they have your father too!
While us?
[SOBS] We've got nothing left!
Look at what we have, Bea!
Nothing!
Ma…
[SOBS]
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Now I understand
why you're so furious at that Billy!
But you should've told me
about it right away!
You knew that your father had come back!
Ma, believe me, I wanted to.
But I wanted to tell you about it
once I'd already avenged you.
That devil-spawn father of yours
is together with Billy's aunt!
I'll kill them!
I'll kill them both!
- [BEA] Ma! Ma!
- [SOBBING]
Ma!
This is what I was worried about!
This is what I was trying to stop!
That's why I didn't tell you about it!
[MARIELA] Am I in the wrong?
It's only right for them to die!
Ma…
Ma.
No one's dying.
No one's dying, okay?
And most of all,
I don't want you to hurt yourself.
What if you end up
trying to kill yourself again?!
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
I won't do it ever again.
I regret doing it.
It's what caused your sister's
death. [SOBBING]
[SHUSHING]
- [SNIFFLING, SOBBING]
- There, there…
That's why, Ma,
you have to promise me.
Please, Ma, promise me
that you'll leave our revenge to me.
I will avenge us.
I will avenge us both, okay?
Ma, please, okay? Please.
Leave it up to me.
I'll do it.
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
[JORDAN] Dude?
- Hey.
- What's up?
Bea and her mom are gone from their place.
- Huh?
- The police went there.
So what now?
How are we going to find them?
Isn't this better?
For them to just go away?
So they won't bother you anymore.
- Dude, come on.
- I'm just worried about you.
Your safety. Look,
I don't want you to get hurt.
I mean, I can't always be there for you.
Okay, Jordan, thank you.
I know you're just concerned.
If it were just about me,
fine, I'd let it slide.
But we're talking about Auntie Pres.
I won't just let it go. Sorry.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[TONI] What a beautiful bouquet!
Who's it from, Val?
Honestly, I don't know.
Wow! Real main character energy, huh?
Wow! You have a new admirer, twinny?
Wait, how come I don't know?
It's not in your vlogs.
Maybe it's from a fan?
Look, there's a letter. Open it.
- Oh, there it is.
- Go.
- [PLAYFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
- [PAPER RUSTLES]
- [CHARM] What?
- Oh…
- What's wrong?
- [GROANS]
- What the…?
It's from Robbie.
Sorry, but…
No.
Wait. Robbie who?
Robbie, as in Jade & Jude's Robbie.
Jordan's bartender.
What a waste.
But hopefully, I'll get one next time.
But I prefer periwinkles.
Robbie, my love, choose me instead.
[PLAYFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[PHONE RINGING]
Billy, we're here.
- Thank you, Billy.
- [BILLY] Oliver.
Remember our deal, okay? Just one hour.
- Can we make it two hours?
- [MOUTH CLICKS]
Don't ask for more.
- You still have homework to do.
- Okay.
You're lucky your sister even let you.
Okay then, Billy, bye now.
- Bye!
- Mm-hmm.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
Come on, let's go inside.
- Pa!
- Are you excited?
Come on, let's go inside.
Chief?
Chief, the draft of our contract
with Sir Peter is ready.
It's in your email for your review.
But I also printed a hard copy.
Okay. Thank you, Blaire.
Okay.
[CHUCKLES]
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
- [UTENSILS CLINK]
- [OLIVER] Hmm, so good!
Oliver, eat slowly.
It's really good, Auntie.
Thank you, Pa.
Do you like it?
The dishes I made
are mostly vegetable dishes.
That's good for you.
Go ahead, keep eating.
What about you? Aren't you going to eat?
- I'm full.
- It's so good.
Auntie…
Can we invite Papa
to my moving-up ceremony?
I got high honors.
Pa, do you want to be the one
to put the medal on me?
What is it?
Aren't you going to be at
my moving-up ceremony anymore?
Are you leaving?
Are you going to leave us again?
Remember this, son.
That won't happen again.
From now on, I'll always be here for you.
Thank you, Pa.
Thank you.
Ah! I have a surprise for you.
- Wait.
- Really?
- What is it?
- Give me five minutes.
- Am I included too?
- Just continue eating.
- Oliver!
- I'll be quick!
We only have 25 minutes left!
- You and your sister agreed!
- This will be quick!
[SIGHS]
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC PLAYING]
Please thank Billy
for giving me the chance
to spend time with Oliver.
I hope one day,
we can patch things up too.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
Don't get your hopes up too much.
Oliver was only given permission
to see you today.
Don't expect him to be allowed
to meet you all the time.
I understand Billy.
I owe her a huge apology.
Billy's mom was pregnant with Oliver
when I walked out on them.
I ran off with another woman to Canada.
We got mixed up in a scam,
and I ended up in prison for a long time.
When I was in prison,
that's where reality hit me.
That's where I learned my lesson.
I was so stupid,
and I was a complete jerk.
I hurt all the people I love.
And now,
I'm paying for all my mistakes.
You're right, Precious.
I deceived you.
I deceived Oliver.
I pretended to be someone else
to be with him.
But what I felt for you…
I didn't mean for it to happen.
I didn't want to hurt you,
but I couldn't tell you the truth either.
But even though I wasn't honest with you,
the love I have for my children
and for you…
is real.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
[OLIVER] I hope Billy is
with us next time.
- Bye, Pa!
- Be good, okay?
[OLIVER] Yes!
Just want to let you guys know that
I'm very excited about this partnership.
Thirty million is a serious investment.
Yes, it is.
[BILLY] Thank you so much again for
your trust. We won't take it lightly.
- [PETER] Right.
- [JORDAN] Yes, thank you.
[PETER]
…as LoveList
goes from a regional brand
to a global brand.
[ALL] Cheers!
- [MARJ] Whoo-hoo!
- [RALPH] Yeah!
- [BILLY] Congrats!
- [RALPH] Whoo!
[PETER] What are
you looking at?
I can't believe you're single.
It's so hot.
So, you believe in online dating?
I hope I can find
my match.
Mm-hmm.